One of the best places to view the cherry blossom
is in Shinjuku Gyoen National Garden.
But we weren’t the only ones with that idea.
We we're not the only ones with that idea.
Luckily, the line wasn’t too bad and moved quickly.
The cherry blossom is in full bloom, and yeah,
a lot of people, very popular park.
We're a bit tired after
all this traveling
so we just wanted to just
relax a little bit,
have a more relaxing day.
So the only engagement that we have for
today is a restaurant,
a yakiniku place and it's
actually won an award for its
performance I guess.
It's also very very expensive,
it's like at least a little over 50,000 yen
for this yakiniku course meal.
I hope it lives up to the hype.
Let's head over there now and I'll see
you guys at the restaurant.
Do you like it?
It's good.
It's really that good?
What is happening...
It just...
It just melts.
Oh lord, I'm a believer.
Overall experience so far has
been out of this world
for me personally, and that's
coming from someone
who just went to Kyoto and
ate some in Kobe
at the Kobe restaurant.
This is better.
I can't recommend this more highly.
Just come here if you're able to,
because wow, so far this is
probably the best
Yakiniku experience I've had in my life.
And that, that says just a lot.
Or maybe it doesn't, I don't know,
but it's very good.
Come here.
We begin the day by
visiting this popular bakery cafe.
We arrived 30 minutes before opening
and were able to get a table.
There was already a long line,
but takeout is available if you don’t want to wait.
The bakery is known for their Totoro-shaped cream puffs.
They come with various filling.
This one has chocolate filling,
A sakura Totoro Cream Puff.
This one has strawberry filling.
A cool place to visit if you're a Studio Ghibli fan.
We also picked up a few cookies to take with us.
We decided to spend some time in Shimokitazawa.
Shimokitazawa is known for
vintage shopping, live music, and casual eateries.
It’s slowly become one of my favorite areas in Tokyo.
Shimo is a very colorful neighborhood,
full of character and personality.
Let's check out a vintage store.
There’s so much stuff here,
but it’s nicely curated, albeit a bit pricey.
That's the thing about Shimokitazawa.
It's not really a place to score cheap thrift deals.
There are much better areas for thrifting such as Koenji.
Shimokitazawa is all about curated American and
workwear vintage at a premium price.
And it comes with a price.
You can easily spend a whole day
browsing through all the vintage stores.
We visit Nakameguro to see
the cherry blossoms along the canal.
The Meguro River is one of the most
popular cherry blossom spots in Tokyo.
In the evening, you can sample
street food along the canal.
There are so many people out tonight.
The restaurant itself is pretty small and
the walls are covered in Beatles posters.
The owner, Susumu Kakinuma,
is a huge Beatles fan.
Kakinuma-san is one of the pioneers
of Neapolitan pizza in Japan.
Seirinkan makes classic Neapolitan pizzas.
A great starting point for exploring pizza in Tokyo.
We ordered the Margherita and the Quattro Formaggi.
We sat right at the bar,
so we could watch all the action.
The pizzas came out looking incredible.
Time to eat.
The pizzas did not disappoint.
Easily one of the best pizzerias in Tokyo.
If you love pizza, this is a must-visit.
We also wanted to sample
some of the food stalls near the canal.
The sticks were surprisingly good.
You're head is not in the frame.
Chandon.
Cheers.
The sparkling wine was a miss.
I've tasted better.
Located in Nagatachō, near
the heart of Japan’s political center.
Hie shrine has a long history,
dating back to the Edo period.
The shrine feels surprisingly quiet
compared to everything around it.
Instead of foxes, this shrine is guarded by monkeys.
They're believed to be messengers of
the gods and symbols of protection.
Sake donated by breweries for good luck.
The shrine is dedicated to
Emperor Meiji and Empress Shoken.
Despite being in one of Tokyo’s busiest areas,
the shrine’s setting within a vast forest
makes it feel surprisingly peaceful.
We just visited the Meji shrine,
one of the main shrines here in Tokyo.
Has been a bit chilly the last two days.
There's like a weird, strange cold front.
We are in the beginning of April,
so it should be a bit warmer,
but you know, that's how weather is.
Bring layers.
Layers is your key to surviving
any weather ordeal,
no matter where you are.
I learned that in Iceland.
We're heading to the Yoyogi
part right now
because we are supposed to
be in full bloom
for the Sakura, the cherry blossom.
So I don't wanna promise that
it's gonna be epic,
but I mean, it should be good.
So let's see.
One of my favorite donut shops in Tokyo.
The coffee is also good.
The donuts are lighter and less sweet
than typical American donuts.
I much prefer this style of donut.
A good donut.
We walked around Shibuya and did some
shopping before our dinner reservation.
I found myself nerding out at GBL,
GBL sells limited-edition Studio Ghibli merchandise.
They had a ton of merch.
And I spent way too long browsing.
I couldn’t resist picking up at least one thing.
Went with the Porco Rosso plane,
the Savoia S.21
It was one of my favorite Ghibli films growing up.
Butagumi is a popular tonkatsu restaurant
located in the Nishi-Azabu district.
You can choose from different cuts and types of pork,
which isn’t that common for tonkatsu restaurants.
There are some detailed instructions
in case you’re unfamiliar with tonkatsu.
Butagumi's signature marinated cherry tomato.
Let's try them.
Flavor bomb.
Complete flavor bomb.
So tasty.
Finally, it's time!
One of the best tonkatsu I've had in Japan.
I just can't believe how good this is.
Went for an evening stroll around a few sakura spots.
We've decided to vist the recent
Borderless exhibition in Azabudai Hills.
Since having been to both Planets and the old Borderless.
I was looking forward to see what was new.
I oddly enjoyed this whole drawing to digital experience.
Pretty cool.
It was cool to visit and see the new displays.
But I'm not sure I would do it again.
I think experencing it once is enough.
Since the weather was so nice,
we made our way to Chidorigafuchi.
It's another popular cherry blossom spot, where you can hop on a rowboat and take it all in from the water.
It was a very busy day.
I think we waited over an hour in line if not more.
Time to row.
Chidorigafuchi is a moat along
the northwest side of the Imperial Palace.
It's considered one of Tokyo’s top sakura spots,
with hundreds of cherry trees lining the moat.
While it was nice to experience.
I'm not sure I'm willing to wait an hour again for this.
Finally, able to visit Udon Shin.
I've heard to much about this place.
This udon bowl was so good.
Hands down the best bowl of udon I've had so far.
This was our final night in Tokyo.
We had to catch the evening flight after this.
Thank you for watching.
I'll see you guys in the next one.